Kostadis Roussos: Hello?
Kostadis Roussos: Hello Nikhil.
Nikhil: Can you post for this?
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, that is a very nice headshot of you.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm almost just like, who is this? That's not him.
Nikhil: I had this picture always.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I know, but I just.
Nikhil: But, okay, yeah, I was turning on the video, so we might have to.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Dungeon.us.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just see, where am I?
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Roll 20.
Kostadis Roussos: Come on, sign in.
Kostadis Roussos: So when my COVID happened, Roll20 got slammed.
Nikhil: When your COVID happened?
Kostadis Roussos: When COVID started.
Nikhil: Right, right, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, what happened was that, like.
Kostadis Roussos: playing on digital tabletop was kind of this boutique thing that pretty much nobody did. And then COVID happened, and now everybody does… now it's become, like, the way you play the game.
Kostadis Roussos: There's people who think that that's bad, there are people who think that's good, I don't know. To me.
Nikhil: I don't know, I'd like to, you know, I like the feel of,
Nikhil: you know, moving the characters, rolling the dice. So, I would still prefer for something, you know, this has got a really good story, so something that has a good story, I feel it should be in person.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I agree. Anyway, I shared with you the Syrinscape link. Let's see if this time it works. All right.
Nikhil: Are you playing something?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I'm not yet. I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I'm just, like, I love this tool, but, like, the UI, I love the audio it's done.
Kostadis Roussos: But it's like, sometimes… Let's see if this will work. Maybe it will or it won't.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Yes, I can hear.
Kostadis Roussos: You can hear it.
Kostadis Roussos: Makes one of us.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you can hear it, which is odd. Now I can' All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Sound settings.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I see the problem. Let me just put that over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, can you hear it?
Nikhil: Yes, I can hear you.
Kostadis Roussos: Excellent.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: So the map…
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: It's very faint. Let me try increase the mobility.
Kostadis Roussos: You can adjust the volume if you want.
Nikhil: Okay, perfect.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, let's go here.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, can I show you how you can roll initiatives so I don't have… Oh, did I already roll initiative?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I don't. Did I roll initiative?
Nikhil: I think we did…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Did I? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, I don't think I rolled for you… you didn't roll initiative, or if you did.
Nikhil: I did, I got a bad initiative, it was a 4.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you did get a 4.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Wait, okay, let's do it again.
Kostadis Roussos: Why don't you roll? Why don't I don't I don't think I think I think that monsters rolled for initiative, but I'm
Kostadis Roussos: You rolled for initiative.
Nikhil: So you were gonna show me how to do that, or.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just, let me just make sure, all right.
Kostadis Roussos: Give me one second.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so if you click on, if you click on your character first and roll 20.
Kostadis Roussos: And then roll initiative, it'll pop the initi- it'll put the initiative directly in there.
Nikhil: I click on the character in the map.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and then click on Initiative in your enrolled in D&D Beyond. It'll do the right thing.
Kostadis Roussos: There we are, I found the initiative, okay.
Nikhil: 20.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so your your initiative should have appeared appeared in the yes.
Nikhil: Oh, this is interesting. So I click on the character and do whatever the action here is.
Kostadis Roussos: matches. Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay.
Nikhil: So what do you do?
Kostadis Roussos: I win.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So this skeleton over here attacks first.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: it picks up its shortbow and fires a bolt at you. That misses spectacularly.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: So, your turn.
Kostadis Roussos: Isn't that right? Whose turn is it.
Nikhil: My turn, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela shouts, If you have a mace, now would be a good time to use it.
Nikhil: I don't have a mace, I don't
Nikhil: I'll use the wax.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay.
Nikhil: I'm rolling for the first time.
Nikhil: Just seven.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a miss. Next attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Would you roll this?
Kostadis Roussos: That's a 20. Alright, roll for Clicking… Okay.
Nikhil: Why is the click not working?
Kostadis Roussos: Because sometimes it doesn't, because it hates you that way.
Nikhil: There we go.
Nikhil: How do I click? Okay, damage. Okay, I'm rolling for damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Eight points, eight points. That's not very good, but that's better than nothing.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: Wait, 8 points of damage does nothing?
Kostadis Roussos: No, I mean, it does, it does, but not.
Nikhil: Shit.
Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming you attacked this guy, because that's the only guy you had advan- you had- you could use your sneak attack bon
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: Is there anything I can do here?
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, okay, so where we did it roll 20
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, where were we? No, no, no, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: The skeleton.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: This skeleton… takes a shot at Pip.
Nikhil: Which one?
Kostadis Roussos: This one here.
Kostadis Roussos: With his shortbow.
Kostadis Roussos: And that is a… I think that's a mess.
Kostadis Roussos: That's his armor class. Yep, that's a miss. All right, Sister Maela.
Nikhil: Thanks.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: walks in front, and will use her Turn Undead facility, her ability to turn undead.
Nikhil: Turn on bed.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. She goes, watch this.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Just do something here.
Kostadis Roussos: Maybe on it.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Any other sidekick?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, actually, they can't turn on that? That's weird.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on. Okay, fine. I'm declaring they should be able to turn undead. Clerics that can't turn undead are kind of point
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Give me a second.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, I just, I just realized I did something with the definition of the, Maela that didn't work. Turn undead, 5th edition, 2nd level.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so it's a
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so it's, she, she stands up in front, she stands in front of, the monsters, and says, BE GONE!
Kostadis Roussos: In the name of my dwarven god.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, no, no, no, that's not, that's not the damage, that's, that's their.
Kostadis Roussos: What's their wisdom? Their wisdom is plus 2, plus 4, 12. Alright, so… two of them failed their saving throws.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, one, two, three, four.
Kostadis Roussos: That's three. This guy failed.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he is frightened
Kostadis Roussos: And then this guy's also frightened.
Kostadis Roussos: Here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you see the two ones with the little dots? They've been frightened, so they're not going to attack you
Kostadis Roussos: Hold me.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: No damage, just frightening.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they're frightened So, as long as you don't attack them, they're not gonna attack you
Kostadis Roussos: And they're going to try to get away as far as they can from Sister Maela.
Nikhil: I see.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: Good work system.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, of course it's good work. That's who I am. All right. Okay. This skeleton runs through here, opens the door and runs through here.
Nikhil: So it's gone.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: This skeleton, on the other hand…
Kostadis Roussos: attacks Zenvon with his short sword.
Kostadis Roussos: And does 11 points of damage. Hold on. Hold on.
Nikhil: Did you just say 11 points?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I said 11 points.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you okay?
Nikhil: Yeah, no, no, I mean, like, 11… I just have got, like, 15 co.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. How many hit points do you have left?
Nikhil: Four.
Kostadis Roussos: all right well sister male is gonna have to heal you next all right BI pip pip all right what does pip do
Kostadis Roussos: Pip uses…
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so Pip.
Nikhil: Let's start with, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: It's Pip and then Veyra. It's Pip and.
Nikhil: And also, I don't see Veyra in the.
Kostadis Roussos: She's right there.
Nikhil: Yeah, also, sorry, sorry, I see it, I see.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, she's there. Alright, so Pip will attack the one you've injured.
Kostadis Roussos: And… kills it!
Kostadis Roussos: He will use an action surge to attack the next one over here.
Kostadis Roussos: and hits it for how much damage?
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Seven, six points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Item number two. Yes. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra has cast Magic Missile twice, but if ever there was a time to cast her last Magic Missile, this would be it.
Kostadis Roussos: So, let's see, how much damage does each bull do? 3. She kills this guy with 2, and wounds this… no, wounds this guy with 3.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, this guy runs over here as well.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: The skeleton.
Kostadis Roussos: marches up… to, I guess…
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on. And then Pip goes over here, because, to protect you a little bit. So the skeleton charges at Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: and attacks with his short sword and misses.
Kostadis Roussos: Mmhm.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he misses. Okay, Xenovon, you're up
Kostadis Roussos: You might want to use Nick this time.
Nikhil: Nick, Nick is possible with the scimitar. Yes, I'll give you the.
Kostadis Roussos: That way you can attack and disengage.
Nikhil: Yes.
Nikhil: It's a 10.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a miss. Roll again for your second attack.
Nikhil: To 90.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a hit. All right, damage. I'm assuming you moved over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Damage?
Nikhil: Damage, 4 plus 5… 12 points.
Kostadis Roussos: Nice! You killed it!
Nikhil: Yay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, there's only one skeleton left.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, well, they're mindless, so…
Kostadis Roussos: I guess they will attack you because you're straight ahead of them all right
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, they, do 6 points of damage, and you… are you… let me ask you a question. You can… are you gonna stay there, or are you gonna move out of the way?
Nikhil: I'm gonna move back. I'm just at 4 points of damage, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you would move back, right?
Kostadis Roussos: So why don't you move somewhere else?
Nikhil: Okay, mobile phone.
Nikhil: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Safe.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… I guess he'll just attack Pip then, for…
Nikhil: Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: No, Pip, because Pip's the closest.
Kostadis Roussos: So Pip take six points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: I will cast healing on you.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Let me just see what she does.
Kostadis Roussos: She will cast Cure Wounds. What is Cure Wounds? Cure Wounds 2D form.
Kostadis Roussos: Can't remember what currency is,
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: 2d8 + 2 2d8 + 2 Root.
Kostadis Roussos: she casts it to D8 You get 10 more hit points, Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: Leaving.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: The skeleton continues to make chatter very far away.
Nikhil: The ones that ran away?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they're still making, they've run away. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip.
Nikhil: About payment plan.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: No, I'm just trying to take care of.
Kostadis Roussos: One.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Pip strikes the creature.
Kostadis Roussos: D20 plus 4.
Kostadis Roussos: and he hits 4d8 + 2 5 points of damage
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra. She's out of magic missiles, but she can still do… this.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a hit.
Kostadis Roussos: What did she do?
Kostadis Roussos: She casts Firebolt.
Nikhil: 2 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: To be fair, it does a lot less damage than the sound effects.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: This skeleton still is out of the way. Zenvon, you're Okay, oh…
Kostadis Roussos: I have a good pick point, but… That's too late.
Nikhil: Yeah, that's.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll use the shorts for… I'll do the wax.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil: Should I move forward, or, like, can I attack from there?
Kostadis Roussos: You have to move forward, I mean, you have to be within 5 feet, right?
Nikhil: Okay, then,
Kostadis Roussos: But if yeah.
Nikhil: I'll do, I'll do the link, okay, so, so.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll come here.
Kostadis Roussos: So you'll have about 20 minutes So…
Kostadis Roussos: I'll use the dagger. All right.
Nikhil: 19?
Nikhil: 24, got it.
Kostadis Roussos: What? Both are damaged.
Nikhil: 5 for 8 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, it dies.
Kostadis Roussos: Good.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, hold on. Let's give you the, the Like a pizza.
Nikhil: This sounds like Rocky Valhalla music.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: This sounds like the Rocky Balboa music, you know, the Rocky movie, when he
Kostadis Roussos: Have you seen it? Okay. Yeah, yeah, no, I've seen it.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, where would you like to go next?
Kostadis Roussos: So.
Nikhil: So… The bottom… East Tour is where the skeleton's from.
Kostadis Roussos: Ember and I are off. Hold on, hold on. Ember and I are going.
Kostadis Roussos: And the English, as is tradition, are taking out their frustrations on the French. I see. It's 4-0. I see.
Kostadis Roussos: Ouch.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, somebody decided to come play a third place game and somebody decided they had better things to do.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Zenvon. Let me just… let me just remind you where you're… here. This is… the three… this is, the Tresander Crypts. It had… there are three large stone sarcophagi,
Kostadis Roussos: And there's these false columns. Do you want to inspect the sarcophagi, or do you want to go through the,
Kostadis Roussos: Or do you want to look at the various slids?
Nikhil: So… Both of the skeletons ran through the open door at the bottom.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: So, first we'll inspect the… Profits, and then,
Nikhil: Go to the same door where the other two skeletons ran away.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so while you're doing that, as you're, as you're digging through that, you find yourself.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, and one of the… one of the…
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: As you're, as you're doing that, the two skeletons appear. Sister Maela goes, huh, apparently they do, they, they don't, they, they,
Kostadis Roussos: The the the they they stop being afraid.
Nikhil: Ohh.
Nikhil: Hey.
Nikhil: I'll deal them with them… deal with them in the next room, but.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, but what you notice is that now in the brighter light, they see that you're wearing red cloaks and choose not to attack you.
Nikhil: Where the light come from.
Kostadis Roussos: While you were looking for things, remember, you can't see in the dark
Kostadis Roussos: Look, they weren't supposed to attack you before, because you were wearing red cloaks, but I forgot, so I'm doing it now, al.
Nikhil: Cool. So they're not gonna attack, and we'll still open the…
Kostadis Roussos: yeah they don't care as long as long as long as you're not doing anything as long as you don't attack them they won't attack you so they're just kind of sitting just over here standing guard against anybody who might be a might be a bad guy might might not be the right leader might not be a red cloak since you're I didn't I missed that detail about the fact that red cloaks don't get attacked by
Kostadis Roussos: caught the skeleton. So consider this a
Kostadis Roussos: So there's a jeweled gold bracelet worth 140 gold piece, which lies among the bones in the sarcophagus containing the human female remains, so let's just add that to the story notes.
Kostadis Roussos: Where are we writing that up?
Kostadis Roussos: Wherever we're keeping track of our treasure, we should put there.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Is it, is it, is it.
Nikhil: Storylines. Storylines.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: 140 gold pieces. Room 5. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Room 6, room 4, rather.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Ahhh!
Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: As you're, as you're digging through that, you do hear some noise coming from the northeastern door.
Nikhil: Please control. Okay.
Nikhil: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Can I go listen?
Nikhil: Have you gotten all the…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you've gotten all the loot from here.
Nikhil: Okay, then yes, I'm gonna go…
Kostadis Roussos: Listen.
Nikhil: What's happening today?
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: 28.
Nikhil: Investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, I was trying to see if I had — hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't have it here we go, that'
Kostadis Roussos: No, that one doesn't work either. All right, anyway, so I was just curious if they had anything.
Kostadis Roussos: What, so what you hear is essentially people,
Kostadis Roussos: You hear people screaming, please help us, please help us.
Nikhil: I think they've been, captured.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that they're as if they're captives.
Nikhil: We can deal with them later.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela says, boss?
Kostadis Roussos: I think we should, help the helpless, you know, we're the good guys, remember?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Well, I'll do this for you, Sister M.
Kostadis Roussos: she got she what she's you.
Nikhil: For you.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, do you want to open the door, or do you want to have Pip open the door?
Nikhil: I will open the door.
Kostadis Roussos: You will open the door. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see. Hold on. Open the door. So.
Kostadis Roussos: because of all the noise you guys made, they were ready for… it turns out there were some bad guys ready for you. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: But nobody is surprised, because they are truly rolled awfully. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Santa Mona, you step inside, and you see, the, you see the following. This long room is partitioned into three areas, with iron balls
Kostadis Roussos: wall bars walling off the north and south filthy straw lines the floors of these cells the hinge doors of which are secured by chains and padlocks a pair of human women are held in the cell to the south while human a human boy is confined to the north
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, a pair of human are held in the soil to the north.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, a human boy… Sorry, you should be over there. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so.
Kostadis Roussos: Initiative, I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: They were waiting, they were trying to surprise you, but they failed.
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Kostadis Roussos: So.
Kostadis Roussos: Trying to ambush you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let's see.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And we'll need these guys initiative, right?
Kostadis Roussos: That should be something.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Zenvon. Hold on.
Nikhil: I think Pip is 15.
Nikhil: Put.
Nikhil: Pip's number is 15.
Kostadis Roussos: No, his is 16.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh wait, did I not put him in? Hold on.
Nikhil: I see.
Nikhil: M12, but not that, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I don't know. For some reason, Pip's number did not… I must have done something there.
Kostadis Roussos: It should be.
Kostadis Roussos: It should be 12.
Nikhil: This is 12, Maela is 10.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on. Pip, Maela is, 15.
Kostadis Roussos: And PIP is 12.
Kostadis Roussos: I see two clicks. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: One as well, please.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, let me just see. Let me just have a look here.
Nikhil: Voyeur has 17…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, this is correct. Xenovon Veyra has 17, Sister Maela has 15, Pip has 12.
Nikhil: Okay, so she has a plus one of the initiative.
Nikhil: Okay, good.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh no, she's got a plus 1, and Pip's got a plus 2. Alright, Zenvon.
Nikhil: Yes, the highest, okay.
Nikhil: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Ohh.
Nikhil: Okay, I gotta be careful, so I'm gonna use my NIC.
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Nikhil: to attack, the Redbrand.
Kostadis Roussos: Number one, and…
Nikhil: Move into the back room, so, you know, like, go back here after attacking.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so you're going to nick, you're going to use your nick.
Nikhil: Yes, I'm gonna use the dagger on him, so I'll roll for that, roll for the hit.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, it's got an armor class of… 11.
Kostadis Roussos: That is…
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm going to put Pip over here, all right.
Nikhil: Damn.
Nikhil: Just.
Kostadis Roussos: 5 points of denture. Not exactly the best roll you could have done.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just make sure you can see the, you know, help.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Nikhil: I still have the second attack, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, how you doing? How you
Kostadis Roussos: Cheap.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Done?
Kostadis Roussos: Zenvon, are you gonna stay there, or are you.
Nikhil: I'm gonna move back.
Kostadis Roussos: Disengage.
Nikhil: It's eng.
Kostadis Roussos: Right!
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: The Redbrand attacks.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the Redbrand attack.
Kostadis Roussos: And he does, what does he do? He attacks, all right, which one is this?
Kostadis Roussos: That one, right? Okay. He, step, he, steps over here and whacks, whacks, Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: With his short sword.
Kostadis Roussos: and misses. But he uses that as an opportunity to come over here, and move over here, so that the next guy can attack. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra.
Kostadis Roussos: Or Sister Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: You got it.
Kostadis Roussos: Where is she? Oh, there she is, she's right there. Alright, Veyra. Veyra, what do you do, Veyra? Veyra, Veyra's like, I don't like this!
Kostadis Roussos: So she's, she's not very happy about this.
Kostadis Roussos: What does she do? What are her spells?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, she's run out of first level spells.
Kostadis Roussos: She is going to disengage.
Kostadis Roussos: And go over here. Alright.
Nikhil: Diamond spells can.
Kostadis Roussos: No, she can cast spells, but, they're ranged spells, so she has a disadvantage, so she doesn't want to be, with her 4 hit points, killed by, you know…
Nikhil: Makes sense, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela, Sister Maela, what does Sister Maela do? She's going to hit with her hammer.
Kostadis Roussos: And that is a hit!
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: He does 6 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: The Redbrand Ruffian.
Kostadis Roussos: Number two.
Kostadis Roussos: He moves over here.
Kostadis Roussos: And he attacks!
Kostadis Roussos: And, he…
Kostadis Roussos: Misses. Alright. He will step over here. Pip, you're up. What do you want Pip to do?
Nikhil: You know. Oh, you mean good. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You tell me what you want to do, and then roll an attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: Yeah, I wanna attack the guy in the, in the clips, in the clip too, so…
Kostadis Roussos: You want to attack the guy in the crew, not the guy who's Wow.
Nikhil: Both are the same guy, right.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, there's two people. There's a guy over here. Let me just show you. There's a guy in here.
Kostadis Roussos: And there's a guy over here. There's, like, number 1, number 2, or.
Nikhil: Right, wait a second.
Nikhil: The guy who was recently injured is the number one.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I want VIP to attack the guide.
Nikhil: Number 1.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Go on, baby.
Kostadis Roussos: Rule of D20, remember.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that is a hit! He does 6 points of damages, and kills him!
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty!
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: This guy… Charges at PIP.
Kostadis Roussos: And,
Kostadis Roussos: Mrs.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Zenvon, you're up.
Nikhil: I think I'm better at predicting bitterness based on that.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Based on the numbers, I'm trying to predict if it's a hit or a miss.
Kostadis Roussos: He missed. Yes, yes. Hold on a second. No, no, no, hold on. No, yeah, he missed. He missed, he missed the…
Nikhil: One minute, I'll just get something. I want to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: Tell me when you're back, yeah?
Kostadis Roussos: It's coming.
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, I'.
Nikhil: Cheers So Nutanix gave this small baseball bat, so I thought of using this as a sword.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Oh, that's my turn to attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: Both of them are inside the room, so…
Nikhil: I'll still use the NIC to move forward.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're gonna move forward over here and attack from over here.
Kostadis Roussos: You can even go over here if you wanted to.
Nikhil: Oh, yeah, yeah, I'll go there, and I want to come back to that room, so I'm gonna.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Nikhil: When I use my dagger.
Nikhil: It was… Okay, thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a hit.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Nikhil: The damage?
Nikhil: 7 points of damage, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you going to move back or?
Nikhil: Minimum back, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, sounds good. All right, Veyra steps over here, casts her fire spell.
Kostadis Roussos: and hits four
Kostadis Roussos: Which is that?
Kostadis Roussos: D10 during.
Kostadis Roussos: And 10.
Kostadis Roussos: for eight points of damage and the guy's down to one hit point
Kostadis Roussos: This time it did sound that way. Alright. Sister Maela.
Nikhil: Who's down, like, 10… the number 2 or the number 3?
Kostadis Roussos: Number 3.
Nikhil: 3, 4.
Kostadis Roussos: He should look like he's down to very few hit points.
Nikhil: No, there are no, help bar on them, so…
Kostadis Roussos: There aren't?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sorry, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Maela. Sister Maela will cast,
Kostadis Roussos: It is.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He blows the saving throw, so she… he takes,
Kostadis Roussos: 5 points of damage of Sacred Flame.
Kostadis Roussos: Is there, like, is there a Sacred Flame sound effect? No, there isn't. Alright, so he takes Sacred Flame and dies.
Kostadis Roussos: All right Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: This guy decides that, you know, he's had better days in his life, so he goes, one, disengages.
Kostadis Roussos: 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Three. Four. Five.
Kostadis Roussos: 6.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Pip turns to you. Are we chasing him, boss, or not?
Nikhil: Wait, where did he run away? Like, which way?
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You gonna chase him?
Nikhil: Not yet,
Kostadis Roussos: Do we want to chase him in case he calls any help or he's only one guy?
Nikhil: city plan.
Nikhil: Quite possible. Okay, yeah, yeah. Two of us will chase them, and two of us…
Kostadis Roussos: Free these people.
Nikhil: So, me and, Veyra will go chase them, you guys free this,
Kostadis Roussos: Pip turns, you're the, you're the guy with the fingers who knows how to open the locks, I'm the guy with the sword that knows how to.
Nikhil: Yeah, okay.
Nikhil: So, you and, veera can go behind the Karimi, and Nela will help.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So a pit runs over here.
Kostadis Roussos: and attempts to thwack him with his sword
Kostadis Roussos: And he hits him for… 9 points of damage, go Pip!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Zenvon, rush in to open the locks.
Nikhil: Interesting.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see what you have to do to open these locks.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll a DC dexterity 10, a 10 DC dexterity check.
Nikhil: exterior teacher.
Nikhil: Wait, there's Dexterity plus 3, and there's Dex plus 5, both.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me share my screen.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yeah, sure, sure, share screen.
Nikhil: You see there's this one.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello.
Nikhil: That's GPT-7 Pro, and this,
Kostadis Roussos: could you go back to what is that one that that could you go to the DC5?
Kostadis Roussos: oh no no no you want the saving throw one that's the one you want.
Nikhil: Dexterity Savings R.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, is it a saving throw? Oh no, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, now, no, hold on, it's not a saving throw, it's a skill check. So yes, you were.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you unlock the door.
Kostadis Roussos: The kid is very happy. Alright, Veyra. Goes, "Yay! I've been saved!"
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Veyra kind of moves over here. She casts her fire spell one more time.
Kostadis Roussos: A Firebolt leaves her hands and hits four.
Kostadis Roussos: Three points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: She's come over here so she's going to try to unlock the doors.
Kostadis Roussos: And she too unlocks. She unlocks it.
Nikhil: You put a different character.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I pulled a different character. You're right. I meant to turn my laptop. All right. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: The Redbrand Ruffian disengages again.
Kostadis Roussos: Jumps.
Nikhil: Shit, okay, he ran again.
Kostadis Roussos: You're right over here.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip, you're up.
Nikhil: Okay, now, I've freed… me and Myra have freed both the…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Until we have enough.
Nikhil: I'm back.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, but it's Pip's turn, so do you want him.
Nikhil: Oh, yes, yes, Pip, great afternoon.
Kostadis Roussos: All righty.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Pip runs over here, and unfortunately, he triggers a trap.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he falls into a pit.
Nikhil: I see, I hear some footstep.
Kostadis Roussos: And he takes, unfortunately, some damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Fortunately, not very much, because I rolled very poorly. He takes 3 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: And he's 20 feet down. Alright, Zenvon, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay,
Nikhil: I'm gonna… my job here is done.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, the, the, the, the people go, all right, wait, you're, you're gonna just leave us here?
Nikhil: Just stay here until I come back.
Nikhil: It's not safe yet for you guys to move out.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. They're like, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Okay, I'm gonna…
Kostadis Roussos: Why do… I see that pit has fallen into the pit. Yes.
Nikhil: And I try to help him.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: Wow.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming you have some rope, or you can, like, help him climb out So that's what you're
Kostadis Roussos: Well, actually, you can, you can… I have a whip, okay, so I'm gonna use the whip as a rope to…
Kostadis Roussos: Kind of.
Nikhil: So that I can pull it off.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so I guess you can… you can dash over here, you pull him up… Alright, that's what he… that's gonna happen in his turn, not now. Alright, he'll be… he… that's what you guys do, he's over here, he's climbed out…
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Veyra.
Kostadis Roussos: Comes over here.
Nikhil: My turn is done.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, your turn is done.
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra has no ability to hit the guy, but I guess if she moved… Let's see, 1, 2, 3, she moves over here, though, she does.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I guess she does. Alright, so, she will attack. She will fire her firebolt.
Kostadis Roussos: And.
Kostadis Roussos: And it misses entirely. It hits the wall instead of him.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: There goes one.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so she's dashed over here. Alright, the Redbrand muff ruffian goes on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to keep chasing him?
Nikhil: So, so we carefully move Pass the trap.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Wait.
Kostadis Roussos: Now that you know where it is, you just, like, sort of walk around it.
Nikhil: Around it, yes, yes, and being more careful…
Kostadis Roussos: Cool.
Nikhil: Avoid any other traps.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil: Did I roll anything for that? I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, you just, you, you, let me just.
Nikhil: Yeah, I don't see anything related to that.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you don't, you don't have
Kostadis Roussos: Once the trap is visible, as it seemed, you could walk around it. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So that's… you can come over here.
Nikhil: No, you're.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I just… yeah.
Nikhil: Oh, it's Pittston? Okay, okay, sure, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Xenovon, you're gonna fall… be right behind Pip?
Nikhil: Yes, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: My sister Maela is cast, I think, her spell to scissor.
Kostadis Roussos: This is their second Curley wounds.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip gets six hit points.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Okay. Do you want Pip to, keep following, to get, keep going?
Nikhil: Yes, yes, I don't see anything where it's leading, but yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Nikhil: House is so big.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip arrives over here.
Kostadis Roussos: This door opens into a five foot landing that is 15 feet above the large cellar with stone steps descending to the floor in two short flights. Another door stands beneath the stairs to the north. A large stone cistern occupies the western part of the room whose walls are lined with kegs and barrels.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so just to make this a little bit more legible.
Kostadis Roussos: This is like at 15 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you see where that number 15 is?
Kostadis Roussos: No, you can't, of course, because that would be too convenient.
Kostadis Roussos: You see that number 15?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so that's 15 feet above the ground, right?
Nikhil: So this is the room and upper floor.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so essentially there are these stairs that will go up to 15 feet and up to the top. You're in the cellar, if you can imagine.
Nikhil: Got it, got it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. And you see a door over here.
Kostadis Roussos: You see a door over there.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You may want to look around to see where your, your, the Redbrand Ruffian went.
Nikhil: Well, I don't have more visibility, I need to come into the room.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, wait, oh, your PIP doesn't show, doesn't have visibility?
Nikhil: Wait, he does, he does, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Okay, so…
Nikhil: the stairs on the right side, but I can see the cellar, right? Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you see that?
Nikhil: I can see the seller, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so that's all you, so yeah, so if you, if you, if, all right, there's a cistern.
Nikhil: So, there is, like, a water…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, this thing over here is what's called a cistern.
Kostadis Roussos: Perfect. Cool.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: And I see some barrels, okay.
Nikhil: The front door onto the west.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Nikhil: Well.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, we'll go to…
Nikhil: And we don't see that guy yet, so…
Kostadis Roussos: No, you don't. So you can try to… so you can… guys could come in and try to investigate to see if you can figure out where he'
Kostadis Roussos: Mmhm.
Nikhil: Yes, yes, role and investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't, you don't find them.
Kostadis Roussos: You can, Veyra tries to help you, so why don't you roll again?
Nikhil: That's true.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Well, with that, you figured out that he went over here.
Nikhil: And we don't have access going upstairs to the 15…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you do. If you go up these stairs.
Nikhil: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You see? Did you see that?
Kostadis Roussos: Here, let me see. Let me see if this will help. Yeah. You see this now?
Nikhil: Right, right, okay, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So what's your plan?
Kostadis Roussos: Cinnamon?
Nikhil: Okay.
Nikhil: Okay, let's follow this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: You're gonna follow this guy? Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Who's gonna, are you gonna, so you're gonna try to listen to the door?
Nikhil: Yes, yes, as always, he would enter the door, so, roll an investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: 19. You hear the… you hear some noises, some discussions.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: Some murmuring behind the door. There's several…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you hear people talking behind the door.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: This guy has told everybody.
Kostadis Roussos: There's no choice.
Nikhil: He leaves us no choice other than to attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you could always say that we've just killed all of your allies, and, you know, maybe you wanna, like, surrender, and, like, we could take you prisoner, and… and investigate you. I mean, there's… there are other options.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil: Okay, but either way, I'm gonna open the.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I did.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you open the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, this guy is actually over here. All right.
Kostadis Roussos: What's your investigation?
Kostadis Roussos: Roll your investigation.
Nikhil: Why do I need to roll investigation?
Kostadis Roussos: They're hiding, so I need to see if you, okay.
Nikhil: They're hiding, okay, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so I need to see if you see them all. So you see everyone but this guy.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, you see.
Nikhil: The guy on to the south?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yeah, he's hidden, the other guys you can see. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. So,
Nikhil: And they do think that… okay, yeah, go ahead, go ahead.
Kostadis Roussos: You're wearing a red cloak. They look at you, and they go… they stop. They say, wait!
Kostadis Roussos: You're one of us!
Nikhil: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, they turned to… Yep.
Nikhil: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: They turn to the other Redbrand. He goes, what do you mean they attacked you, man? Are you sure these are the guys that attacked you?
Kostadis Roussos: This guy stands up and says.
Kostadis Roussos: Do I look like I'm the kind of person who would lie? That is a killing machine! Kill him!
Nikhil: Okay, so it's my turn.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, so now, so let me just explain to you the situation in case I haven't done it.
Nikhil: No, I understand.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, okay, okay, great, alright.
Nikhil: So, yeah, so he's saying, the Red Rand ran to the bandits and told that, we attacked them. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So, here's what I'm gonna say.
Nikhil: We, we, we are one of you guys, like, come on, we have, we all have the same dress, and look, look at this guy, this guy has turned a traitor. He was, trying to, I, I saw him letting in, letting someone in, so that's why I wanted to catch him and, you know, eliminate him.
Nikhil: So, he's the bad guy.
Kostadis Roussos: That is very clever. That is extremely clever. Roll your deception with advantage.
Nikhil: It worked.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Let me see. I need some names now.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm doing great.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you very much.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I did.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that's fine, do it on Monday. I was going to pick up the car on Friday of next week. Or Saturday, rather.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, I was Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, thanks.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you still there?
Kostadis Roussos: Hello?
Kostadis Roussos: Nikhil.
Kostadis Roussos: Turn off your video.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello?
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, I'm back. No, it's fine. No, it's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Just give me a second.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: See what happens. All right, so,
Kostadis Roussos: They, the, the, the, the, the, one of the red, one of the bandits, they, they, they all approach the other guy very, you know, with their blades pulled out.
Nikhil: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, he's going to, of course, try to defend his honor. What did you roll for deception? Okay, he will try to roll a higher persuasion.
Kostadis Roussos: And he fails.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: Meanwhile, after you freed everybody.
Kostadis Roussos: Two of the, the prisoners, the prisoners' voices are heard in the background.
Nikhil: Why are they here?
Kostadis Roussos: Because they, you know, they… who do you think they're gonna… actually, no, they didn't. Actually, get back, they're not, because when they tried to escape, what happened was the skeletons moved in to attack them, and so now the skeletons are over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Sweet.
Nikhil: Comment at the system.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so they're not in there, they're not in the cellar, I just remembered. They would be trapped in the prison because the skeletons, once they saw them with no cloaks, would start attacking them, right
Kostadis Roussos: So you're saved. So you're saved. All right, gentlemen. They've now, surrounded him.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you gonna…
Nikhil: Are they gonna kill him?
Kostadis Roussos: Yum.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so he goes, so the, the, the bandit whose name is Dessa.
Kostadis Roussos: Rook.
Kostadis Roussos: Says… Says,
Kostadis Roussos: About time somebody cleaned house, which I'm going to cut this rat into several pieces.
Kostadis Roussos: The other bandit looks at him a little bit more carefully, goes, hmm, traitor.
Kostadis Roussos: Funny.
Kostadis Roussos: Nobody sent word down, but it's not very convincing when he's covered in blood and you're covered in blood.
Kostadis Roussos: Where am I, I'm gonna have to go check, I'm gonna go have to check this story to see if it's real.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you gonna let him check or are you gonna try to bluff him again?
Nikhil: Oh.
Nikhil: Alright, I'll… I'll join with you. Let's go check,
Nikhil: Let's confirm your suspicions, and I'll try to take the bandit along with me. I'll go along with the bandit.
Nikhil: So, as soon as this guy is trying to step, steps into the cellar.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil: I'm gonna go behind him and attack him, so that's the plan.
Kostadis Roussos: I figured as much, okay.
Nikhil: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see, okay, so.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming you're going to… okay, so he walks over here. Are you going to attack him, or are you going to let the other… the rest of your party.
Nikhil: Stop.
Kostadis Roussos: Because they can see you from there, remember.
Nikhil: Oh, I see, okay, okay.
Nikhil: No, as soon as he's out of the site, I want to attack.
Kostadis Roussos: But if you attack, they will see you attack from where you currently are.
Nikhil: Yeah, definitely not from there, but…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but if you move out of the way, they might become suspic.
Nikhil: And.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling you.
Nikhil: Yeah, yeah, I'll let my team attack him.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, roll, roll pick.
Nikhil: Okay, hold on. As soon as he is close to the stairs, where Maela and Veyra are there, that's when I attack. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: that's okay so roll roll to hit roll pip roll for pip to hit all right roll D20 plus four
Kostadis Roussos: 12.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, that is a hit. Roll for damage. D8.
Kostadis Roussos: Plus 2.
Kostadis Roussos: 6 points of damage. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra.
Kostadis Roussos: I was very annoyed.
Nikhil: I don't see the bar on it. Let'.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you don't see the bar in him. Huh.
Nikhil: I need the bar.
Kostadis Roussos: You need the bar.
Kostadis Roussos: How are you doing?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, hold on. I'm clicking the wrong button.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm…
Kostadis Roussos: This guy gets to test the roll initiative. Okay, I'm gonna give him… I'm going to assume he was not expecting you guys to be attacked
Kostadis Roussos: Veyra tries to hit him with the dagger and misses. Sister Maela.
Kostadis Roussos: Swings with her mace, and misses! Alright, he screams for help!
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Oh, I said, oh, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so we roll for initiative now.
Kostadis Roussos: The other two, the other two go, the, the, the, the Redbrand says, I told you these guys weren't to be trusted.
Nikhil: It should show now.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, it is a Shenzhou.
Nikhil: the weekends away.
Kostadis Roussos: What? Somebody kicked me.
Nikhil: is useless.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, you did decide to backstab them.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, Xenovon, you're up.
Nikhil: Okay, I rolled for initiative right here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yes, I need you to roll for, oh, yes, I need you to, I rolled, I rolled for, you need to roll for initiative, roll your initiative
Kostadis Roussos: They're on.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, Pip's got 20.
Kostadis Roussos: Sister Maela's got 8.
Kostadis Roussos: Arrow's got… Six.
Kostadis Roussos: And Sister Maela's got four.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, we got Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: hits the guy he… the guy he's hitting, and kills him. Alright. Pip then goes 1, 2, 3, 4…
Kostadis Roussos: 5, 6, and stands there, ready to help you. Alright, Xenomon, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Cinnamon?
Nikhil: Yes, sorry, I'm just planning my strategy.
Nikhil: I think it reached zero.
Nikhil: I can move forward, I'm gonna use the…
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Nikhil: Nikhil Wex.
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Nikhil: WEX is when I can come back.
Kostadis Roussos: No, Nick is when you can come back.
Nikhil: I'm gonna use my dagger, so I'm gonna rolling for What's a.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that's a hit. Good damage.
Kostadis Roussos: 12 points of damage, you killed him!
Nikhil: Step back.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Just move, move, move your character back. Alright, you gonna stay over there? Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see, what does this guy do
Kostadis Roussos: Wick.
Kostadis Roussos: Decides to attack the Redbrand.
Kostadis Roussos: And kills him.
Kostadis Roussos: There he goes. What? He kills the Redbrand.
Nikhil: That was interesting, actually. He actually believed our story.
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Kostadis Roussos: What he believes is, he goes, so look, I helped you, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you know, I, I, I didn't, I, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Glasstaff? Man, he's like some scary shit, and I don't want to be here anymore, and I don't really want to die for him, so
Kostadis Roussos: I did you a solid, and you're gonna do me a solid, and let me leave, and pretend you never saw me.
Kostadis Roussos: Sounds…
Nikhil: A little bit of fair in what… I mean, there's a little bit of fairness in what you're saying, but
Nikhil: We need you. Tell me more about, Glasstaff and Spider, and anything else that you know, and we'll let you know.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Our… the other thing is, stay with us. We have got a lot of gold coins, silver pieces, and a lot of, you know, treasure that we have…
Kostadis Roussos: Earn through our adventure, and you can get a share of it.
Nikhil: Be a nice guy with us.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you want to recruit him?
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that was unexpected.
Nikhil: Excuse.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, what does Wick know about Glasstaff? Let me just see.
Kostadis Roussos: Give me a second. I need to think about it for a second.
Kostadis Roussos: Was this unusual of recruiting someone?
Kostadis Roussos: Unexpected.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, it's his choice, he can either…
Nikhil: At which point, we don't know… I mean, I cannot guarantee anything, or you can join us.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so he goes…
Kostadis Roussos: Glasstaff? He's a wizard, not just a muscle with a title. I've seen him drop a man with a spell, no weapon drawn, nobody messes with him twice.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm…
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, there's more than what… you know, this has got… this dungeon's got multiple levels, you already know this. Wick's only ever been sent to the… I've only been sent to the subterranean part once to carry supplies, and I don't want to go back.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't know what's there, but it's kinda wrong. There's something really wrong over there that messes with your head, I'm told.
Kostadis Roussos: Then he…
Kostadis Roussos: So then you asked about who does he report to, right? He goes, yeah, Glasstaff answers to somebody. I've overheard him complaining about orders from town, and once about the boss's business…
Kostadis Roussos: But, I mean, I think it's somebody in Phandelin, but I don't think, I don't think Glastap
Kostadis Roussos: You asked about the Black Sparta, right?
Nikhil: Black Spider.
Kostadis Roussos: He kind of flinches when you say it.
Kostadis Roussos: But… Kind of as if he could feel some… you could see how uncomfortable that name makes him.
Kostadis Roussos: But he doesn't know anything about it. Do you want to press him on the topic?
Nikhil: Yes, I want to question on the topic.
Nikhil: So we'll… Insight, or investigation, what do I do?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, roll the insight.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, no, just roll intimidation.
Nikhil: Intimidation. Oh, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Or persuasion, whichever one you want.
Nikhil: Integration.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he goes, look dude, I just carry crates, alright? You start asking about the boss's boss, that's how people end up carrying less.
Nikhil: It's.
Kostadis Roussos: Anything.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: It's not giving me any information.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, because he's a low-level th.
Nikhil: I know, I know, I'm still thinking what to do.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you told him that you have gold and treasure, and you'd hire him, so he's kind of looking forward to that.
Nikhil: Okay. Are you really interested to join us?
Kostadis Roussos: He's a role, role in investigation or insight.
Kostadis Roussos: With advantage.
Kostadis Roussos: Investigation.
Kostadis Roussos: That said, okay. He says yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And what are we doing?
Nikhil: Oh.
Nikhil: In order to trust you, you're gonna tell me all the secrets about this manor? Like, what's upstairs?
Kostadis Roussos: Wait, hold on, hold on, Hilton
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, you, okay, he says yes, but you know he's lying. What you really, the impression you get is he's gonna take whatever money you have and get out of, get out of Dodge as fast as possible.
Kostadis Roussos: Is Brey.
Nikhil: He gives.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil: Is that the impression he's giving?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, not that he'll betray you, but that he wants to.
Nikhil: Are you taking our money? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you're offering it to him, he is, he is a cr.
Nikhil: I get it, yeah, yeah, okay, good.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, I'm just telling you, so
Kostadis Roussos: So he takes your money and says, of course I'm with you, boss. And then at his first opportunity, he's going to run away
Kostadis Roussos: But you definitely do not get the impression that he's gonna try to backstab you. He's basically looking at the money as a way to get out of here.
Nikhil: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: Irish pencils.
Kostadis Roussos: So what do you want to do with him? Do you want to let him… do you want… do you give him the money and let him follow you, or are you
Kostadis Roussos: Or let him run away. He's just one lowly thug.
Nikhil: This is such a tough choice. Hold on.
Nikhil: I wanna, you know, try to get more information from him, so…
Nikhil: I wanna tie him up and, you know.
Nikhil: Shove his face into the system and
Nikhil: Get more information from you.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, the only additional piece of information, he's kind of, like, really upset over this at this point in time. He's, like, shitting his pants, and he says that there was this family, the Dendars, that the Redbrands handled a while back.
Kostadis Roussos: 100 wire buttons.
Nikhil: Behind us? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that's the family you guys rescued. Right, okay, that makes sense, okay. Alright, he doesn't have anything else, so you're gonna have to decide what you want to do with him. Okay, cool,
Nikhil: Yeah, I mean, I would prefer to attack him at this point instead of letting him run away.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you're going to attack him. Alright, roll for… alright, you kill him. He's a poor, defenseless guy. He's dead.
Kostadis Roussos: We don't have, we don't have to roll for, combat. Okay! And with that, we are, we are, we, we just have a couple, we just have to explore these two rooms. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's look into room number 1.
Nikhil: Did we get anything here? There are so many crates and barrels.
Kostadis Roussos: Not to check that, dude. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, it turns out that the barrels have, like, food and things like that, right?
Kostadis Roussos: But you do notice a waterproof satchel which hangs from a submerged rope attached to the south wall of the cistern about 2 feet below the water's surface.
Kostadis Roussos: Umm.
Kostadis Roussos: You find inside of it a satchel hidden… you find a satchel which contains a potion of healing and a potion of invisibility.
Kostadis Roussos: Ocean of Healing. Put those.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty. Alright, and in the other room.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you find coin on the various bandits.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just show you what the coin is.
Kostadis Roussos: For the punishment I'll put it up with…
Kostadis Roussos: all right I'll just okay you find various coin here
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, do you wanna go, rescue the family that you just… that is currently being, held by the zombies? By the skeletons?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Nikhil: What's the coin you said?
Kostadis Roussos: I put it in the chat, I put it in the
Kostadis Roussos: 16 silver pieces, 7 gold pieces is in one, 12 gold pieces and… 12 silver pieces and 5 gold pieces in the other, and the third holds 20 copper pieces, 11 electrum pieces, and 2 garnets worth 10 gold pieces each.
Nikhil: What are you describing, like, 1, 2, 3, 5, 2, 3?
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, on the bodies of the, the, the, the bandits.
Nikhil: Oh, okay, okay, each one of them had these… Perfect, okay, so we are gonna head back upstairs to…
Kostadis Roussos: You're downstairs, you mean. You're gonna go back over here, right Read it back.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? To go rescue the, to go rescue, the family?
Nikhil: That's upstairs.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's, it's downstairs,
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let me just…
Nikhil: the below one.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so here is… here… this is zero feet.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: That's 0 feet, and that's 15 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: And this is 10 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Nikhil: Sure.
Kostadis Roussos: no so if you want to go to them you have to this this doorway is at the at zero feet okay
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and the the the family that you you left is over here.
Kostadis Roussos: That make sense? Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Nikhil: I'm gonna move it to this room.
Kostadis Roussos: Move into that room. All right, the two skeletons are like poised at the door.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you're probably gonna have to kill them, because they are, they are definitely now, like, they're, they're currently at the door and they're not moving from it.
Nikhil: Yes.
Nikhil: Initiative, or just.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, hold on, you may not have to, like, you can try to move, I mean, I'm just.
Nikhil: So,
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see,
Nikhil: Something from my portion of the visit will be.
Kostadis Roussos: No, my point is that you know that they weren't supposed to attack the folks with the red blank, so you could see if they're going to attack.
Nikhil: Okay, so, yeah, looks like they might follow my orders, or try to…
Nikhil: Go forward and, ask them to move out.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, they definitely don't ask, they don't listen to you, but they definitely don't attack you.
Kostadis Roussos: Try to open the door.
Nikhil: Yeah, I opened the.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you try to open the door, and it's being held tight on the other side. You're gonna have to tell the people that, you know, it's you, because they're.
Nikhil: Oh, okay, yeah.
Nikhil: Hey guys, it's me. I came back for you. It's all safe now.
Nikhil: You can let go of the door. Let me help you.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you walk inside, right? The skeleton sees you walk inside, and once it sees you walk inside, the skeleton decides that it's, you know, it goes back into its resting position.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming you don't attack them as they move away.
Nikhil: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Ready?
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, and we shall stop here, because it's 4 o'clock, and we've been at it for an hour and a half.
Nikhil: Okay, okay, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you have fun?
Nikhil: Yes, I did. No cliffhanger this time, which is a good thing.
Nikhil: No cliffhanger.
Nikhil: This time.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, okay.
Nikhil: Yes, I mean, I don't… it doesn't have to be every time.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. All right, sir. Take care.
Nikhil: Thanks, host, for this. Take care.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye-bye. Yeah, you too.